{"data":[{"question":"His promotion to manager was a popular ________.","a":"appoint","b":"appointed","c":"appointment","d":"appointee","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Noun phrase: (a\/an) adj + noun.\u00a0\n- Appointment: when someone is chosen for a position or job.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"A holiday in America can be ________ cheap.","a":"surprise","b":"surprised","c":"surprising","d":"surprisingly","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Surprisingly: used as an adverb to add more information for adjective","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"My colleagues are very pleasant, but the manager was a little ________.","a":"unfriendly","b":"friendly","c":"friendship","d":"friendless","answer":"1","explain":"\n- But: implies negative meaning.\u00a0\n- Unfriendly: not kind or friendly.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"I ________ this morning, and was late for school.","a":"sleep","b":"slept","c":"overslept","d":"oversleep","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Simple past tense: Use the Simple Past to express the idea that an action started and finished at a specific time in the past (this morning).\u00a0\n- Oversleep: to sleep for longer than you intended.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"Mr. and Mrs.Brown are a ________ couple but they are very kind to their neighbors' ________.","a":"child \/ children","b":"children \/ children","c":"childish \/ child","d":"childless \/ children","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Noun phrase: (a\/an) adj + noun.\u00a0\n- Childless: having no children (childless couple\/woman\/marriage).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"The air is naturally ________ by foreign matter such as plant pollens and dust.","a":"contaminated","b":"contaminate","c":"contamination","d":"contaminating","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Passive voice with simple present: is\/am\/are + Past participle.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"The heavily ________ atmosphere in some industrial regions is called \"smog\", a word derived from \"smoke\" and \"fog\".","a":"pollute","b":"polluted","c":"pollution","d":"pollutant","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Noun phrase: (the\/a\/an) adj + noun.\u00a0\n+ Polluted: dangerously dirty and not suitable for people to use.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"Why are you always jealous ________ other friends?","a":"with","b":"of","c":"for","d":"to","answer":"2","explain":"\n- To be jealous of: feeling angry and unhappy because someone has something that you wish you had.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"The form-master was suspicious ________ my intention.","a":"about","b":"of","c":"on","d":"a & b are correct","answer":"4","explain":"\n- To be suspicious of\/about: thinking that someone might be guilty of doing something wrong or dishonest.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"He is confident ________ his success in the final examination.","a":"about","b":"of","c":"on","d":"a & b are correct","answer":"2","explain":"\n- To be confident of: sure that something will happen in the way that you want or expect.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"}]}